(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
ROB: It's 6:42 a. m.
Beth's Dad's place.
(EXHALES)
He's out of town.
And it's already a good day.
(SOFTLY) Beth.
(CHUCKLES)
- Rob, what are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Well, then stop.
- That's...
- Stop it.
She's shy.
I could just see this
ending up on the Internet.
ROB: Well, fine, cover up. See if I care.
- I'm interested in other things.
- Like what?
Like you.
- Oh, man.
- That was close.
Do it really... I'm scared of it.
- It's only 30 minutes out.
- Shut up. I've never been.
You've never been to Coney Island?
Oh, how have you
never been to Coney Island?
I don't know, I just... I've never been.
Oh, that's... It's so much fun.
I'm taking you. We're going.
Oh, my God.
You're so excited about this.
- Yeah, I can't wait to...
- Give me this.
What are you doing? What?
Oh, all right. Well,
then from the neck up, okay?
That's the only way I consent to this.
(GIGGLING) Oh, please, Rob,
nobody's paying for that online.
You've never been to
Twelve-Chest-Hairs. com, have you?
- Okay. What else?
- What else, what?
Other than cotton candy
and Tilt-A-Whirls?
- What do you want to do today?
- If I answer that...
JASON: All right, is this thing on?
LILY: Look out!
JASON: Babe, it's not my camera.
I don't know if it's the on button
or the zoom button.
All right. Here, here, here.
I think I got it. Is this on?
Oh, perfect. And now we can have
a nice record of you getting run over.
Is that funny?
(LAUGHING SARCASTICALLY)
JASON: What time is everybody
starting to show up?
- It's getting late here.
- LILY: A couple hours.
- That's why we have to hurry.
- Where are we going?
We're going... We're just going
around the corner to the store!
LILY: I want you to go around
with your brother's camera
and get testimonials from everyone.
JASON: Why? I mean,
it's not like this is a wedding.
(INDIAN MUSIC PLAYING)
LILY: I know it's not a wedding.
I said like a wedding.
I can't get this.
I don't get... I mean,
I don't understand why I have to do it.
'Cause, I mean, I don't...
I don't even know how to work this...
- That's what I think is gonna happen.
- No, I'm not!
- ROB: You totally are. You...
- You have no clue!
LILY: Okay, well,
let me ask you a question.
Can you see me through the viewfinder?
Yeah. Got you.
Good. Now can you see me trying
to carry these bags all by myself?
You're doing a great job.
Here, practise doing two things at once.
JASON: That's good! That was good.
MAN: Thank you.
JASON: I'm not lugging this thing around
- all night long.
- LILY: He is your brother.
This is important. Stop freaking out.
JASON: I understand that, Lily,
but it's a shit job!
- No, it isn't.
- Yes, it is! I'm not doing it!
Jason, I have been planning this
for two weeks!
- All I want you to do is help me.
- Okay, babe, babe.
Okay. All right? I'll do it. It's fine.
I really pissed her off.
Babe, come on.
I was just kidding! Come on!
JASON: Hud? Hud, listen to me.
I got a job for you.
I already have got a job.
- I'm doing the sign, so...
- Yeah, no. I see that,
but this is more important than the sign.
You know how, like, at weddings,
people give testimonials
to the camera, right?
No.
All right. You're gonna take the camera
and just, you know, go around the party
and film people wishing Rob good luck.
I don't know, man.
- That's a lot of responsibility.
- This is important.
And then you have
to do it the whole night...
And Marlena's gonna be here.
- She is?
- Oh, yeah. She is.
- So you're gonna take that.
- Oh, hold on.
- And you're gonna talk to her...
- I didn't...
- For Rob.
- I didn't say I would do it.
- JASON: Just try it out.
- All right, I'll do a few.
JASON: You can, just do mine...
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, go.
All right.
Rob, I don't even know what to say, bro.
Best of luck in Japan.
I love you so much,
and I'm proud of you.
- That's it.
- That's it?
- Yeah. Easy enough.
- Yeah. It's actually kind of fun.
- You enjoy it, Hud.
- Thanks, man.
HUD: Yeah, I'm doing...
MAN: Hey, what's up, man?
HUD: Hey, guys? Hey.
- What do we say?
- Anything.
Bon voyage, Rob.
Or however you say that in Japanese.
(BOTH SPEAKING JAPANESE)
HUD: Yeah, good.
Oh, yeah, all right. Oh, yeah...
(TAPER JEAN GIRL
PLAYING ON STEREO)
- Hud, what are you doing?
- I'm documenting the night.
But I thought I asked Jason to do that.
Oh, yeah, well, Jason asked me to do it,
so I've been doing it.
I've been doing it really well.
Well, are you gonna
take it seriously, though?
Because it's really important.
No, of course. I've been taking it
really, really seriously.
- Very seriously.
- You promise?
Yeah, you wanna do
your testimonial now?
- Okay.
- Yeah, do it right now.
Okay.
Okay, just open up to him,
'cause this is gonna be
- the last thing he sees you...
- Okay, Hud, I got it.
Robert Hawkins,
I can't believe you're leaving me
to look after your brother by myself.
Oh! Easy, easy. I mean
I'm obviously standing right here...
And I know we're not officially family,
yet, but...
- Not fair, 'cause I'm gonna...
- HUD: Dude.
- Okay.
- HUD: I'll cut him out later.
But I think of you as my brother,
and I hope you think of me as a sister.
So, you better call us.
Now that you have this job,
you can afford to call us, so...
- Hud?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sorry. No, you're good.
You're good. You're good.
- That was good!
- That's it?
I thought that was really, really good.
Yeah, but you weren't even paying
attention for...
(BEAUTIFUL GIRLS PLAYING)
HUD: Okay. Okay, you can do this.
Yeah. You got this, man. You got this.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, what's up, dude?
What's up?
Excuse me! Hey, Marlena?
- Hey, what's up?
- Hi. Hi.
Hey, did you know that I'm going around
the party and I'm...
Do you know Rob's leaving?
- Like it's his going-away party.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Cool. Hey, so we're taping,
I think, people talking about him.
Oh, no, thank you.
I barely even know Rob.
I'm just coming to say hi to Lily,
so it's a little weird,
if I'm even on it, I think, but thanks.
Okay, cool,
except I'm supposed to get everybody.
So have you ever been to a wedding?
No, I get what you're doing. I just...
I don't want to do it, but thank you.
Okay, cool.
We'll just do a short one real quick.
Okay.
Hey, Rob, Marlena.
I think we've met, like,
probably three times before, total,
and every one of those times
I was really drunk,
so I don't really even know what to say.
But you have a cool job!
That's something!
- Like you're president of something!
- Vice president!
Also really cool.
So good luck with that
and we're gonna be here
keeping New York really safe
and fun for you when you come back.
- Cool, that was a really good one.
- Yeah?
Yeah, we can do
another one if you want.
Do you actually have,
like a card or something?
Well, my agency... We're leaving.
We're going on this stupid retreat
and they like all this video,
- like, bonding crap.
- Oh, yeah. I'm actually...
- I'm not a professional.
- What?
- I'm not a professional. I'm Hud.
- Hug?
No, no, no, Hud.
I'm Rob and Lily's friend.
- We met, like, several times before.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you have the camera
in front of your face,
- it's probably why I didn't...
- Okay, here. If I move it?
- Oh, yeah. What's going on? Totally.
- Yeah.
Yeah, cool. It's nice to see you again.
- Really good to see you. Really good.
- So what have you been up to?
I actually... I'm gonna just go
grab some food,
but good luck with the...
I could still do your
agency's retreat if you wanted...
LILY: He's coming up the stairs right
now. Everybody get ready. Get ready.
Can someone turn down
the music, please?
(MUSIC STOPS)
(PEOPLE SHUSHING)
ALL: Surprise! Surprise!
(ALL CHEERING)
HUD: No, no, no, no, no, no!
How did you guys plan all this?
Easy, you're naive. Let's go.
- Hey. How are you?
- JASON: Take this. Take this.
- I'm sorry. Yes. Thank you.
- What's up?
Oh, hey. Yes. Good.
- What's up, man?
- MAN: Speech!
HUD: Yeah, speech! Speech!
ALL: Speech! Speech!
- Oh, this is very surprising...
- MAN 1: I hope so.
- Obviously.
- MAN 2: It's a surprise party.
Yeah.
But it's very sweet. So thank you. Lily?
LILY: It was everyone. It was everyone.
No, thank you, everyone.
Thank you. It's...
Oh, it means a lot, so... That's it.
That's all I got. I don't know.
- Have a good time!
- HUD: Yeah, party!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yeah!
- Hey, man. Were you surprised?
- Yo. I was, like, not even surprised.
No? Can you describe your current
emotions right now?
I don't know. I would say blasé.
Like, I'm a little... I'm just a little bored.
- No, you're not. Well, congrats.
- No, man, that was awesome, dude.
What are you doing
with the video camera
- by the way?
- I'm documenting the night
so that you can take it
to Japan with you.
Oh, can I watch it every night
- when I get there?
- Jason asked if I...
- Yeah, you could.
- Oh, good.
All right, thank you. Cool.
Hey, Hud, do you know
if Beth's coming tonight?
Yeah, I guess. I'm sure Lily invited her.
Why wouldn't she be here?
(TEAR THE ROOF OFF THE SUCKER
PLAYING)
So how are you
gonna survive without Rob?
- He's like your main dude.
- HUD: Yeah, I know.
Hey, how am I gonna
survive without you?
- I don't know. I'm like your main dude.
- Straight up.
(19-2000 PLAYING)
- As I make my... I'm not here.
- Hi, Hud.
I'm just documenting. Not here.
JASON: That was my biggest problem
is that she picked him...
You know what.
No, but when he said My Fair Lady...
- I love My Fair Lady.
- I was like, "Really?"
That was wonderful.
But, I mean, it worked out, right?
Beth, hey! You made it.
JASON: It doesn't matter, dude,
you're here. All is well.
ROB: Oh, no, it's good. It's good.
- Enjoy it. Have fun.
- Oh, I will. I'm just gonna go say...
- Who is that guy?
- I don't know. He's random.
Here, I'm gonna go check it out.
Look out, documenting.
Oh, thanks.
- I missed your surprise.
- Oh, that's okay.
I'm sorry. No, we had cab problems.
I'm really sorry.
- That's fine.
- Decorating's mine.
- No, that's fantastic.
- Rob, this is Travis.
- Hi.
- Hi. Oh, pleasure.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Congratulations, by the way.
- Thank you.
- Vice President. That's fantastic.
- I love your dress.
- Thank you. I love yours.
- Yeah, thank you.
That's really amazing.
- Should we...
- Yeah, there's a buffet.
Hey, I'm documenting the night.
I'm Hud.
- Okay.
- So, there's tons of sake.
Yeah, just help yourselves, enjoy.
- Enjoy, everybody.
- It's good to meet you.
- Have a good one, yeah.
- Thanks for coming.
- I think he just said I was cute.
- HUD: Are they dating?
Yeah.
(THE UNDERDOG PLAYING)
- Hey, is everything cool, man?
- Yeah, everything's cool.
Okay, because... I don't know,
because you been over here kind of...
Is that my camera?
I don't know. Your brother gave it to me.
Did you switch the tape?
Because I had a tape in there.
I don't know. Was...
ROB: Roller-coasters are fun, but, like,
any kind of tea-cuppy thing...
Tape was in here when I got it. Why?
- Rob, why?
- No, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't... It's stupid.
Okay, are you sure you're cool?
Because you're really weirding me out.
Like, we haven't been
hanging out or anything.
- Here. Here, man. Come on.
- All right, cool. That's more like it.
Excuse me. Sorry. Excuse me.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey, Beth! Beth. Beth. Beth.
Hey, I'm filming goodbyes for Rob.
Do you want to say something?
Oh, Hud, I don't know.
It's not a really good time right now.
Come on, he's leaving.
- I mean, can we...
- I know.
You're not gonna be able
to talk to him for a while.
Isn't there something you wanna say?
You know what?
Travis, can you get me a drink?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, of course.
- Is that... Okay.
Cool, thanks.
Okay, let's... Right here? I don't...
- No, we can do it in the kitchen.
- Okay, perfect.
Okay.
Rob,
I didn't want to do this on camera.
But, I just... I just want you to know
how happy I am for you,
because I know how hard
you've worked for this job
and I know how much it means
to you and...
And I'm really gonna miss you.
Hey. Can I talk to you for a second?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Jason? There's something totally weird
going on with Rob and Beth.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm serious. They're right outside.
- Hud! Not now.
- Okay. I'll check it out.
You never even called me, Rob!
You go and bring some guy to my party?
Hold on! You haven't
talked to me in weeks!
- Hud, man! Come on!
- Sorry!
- What? What?
- I got it. I got it. Hud, get back inside.
- But I'm documenting!
- Not this.
Lily, do you know what
they were fighting about?
Lily, if you know,
you have to tell me. Lily!
I'm not telling you.
I really should know,
as the guy documenting this.
She was the one
who brought me back inside.
- Okay, fine. We'll go find out.
- I'm positive. I promise.
- We'll ask her. We'll go find out.
- She's in the kitchen.
- What?
- Lil!
Lil, do you have something to tell us?
- No.
- You do, don't you?
- What? No.
- Hud, you're a genius.
- You're dodging the question right now.
- There is nothing to tell you.
- Nothing.
- Liar.
Lily, if you know something,
you have to tell us.
- No.
- Look at me.
- Lily.
- I know you. Babe.
Okay, fine, but not on camera.
I'm not telling you on camera.
Okay, that's not a problem.
All right, no problem.
HUD: Why would we say anything?
- JASON: We won't say anything.
- Rob and Beth slept together.
- Are you serious?
- LILY: It happened a few weeks ago.
Beth made me promise
not to say anything.
JASON: Are you kidding me, Lily?
Rob and Beth sleep together,
you're not gonna tell me?
- HUD: Why wouldn't you tell me?
- Why wouldn't I tell you?
Okay, you guys,
don't ask me where I heard this.
Rob and Beth totally had sex together.
- I knew it.
- Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not kidding.
This is extremely serious.
Hey, Marlena.
- It's me, Hud, from before.
- Hi. Right.
Did you know
that Rob and Beth had sex?
- No.
- Yeah, isn't that crazy?
- They've been friends forever.
- Crazy.
I mean, Rob's been in love
with her since college.
Well, maybe it was like
a going-away present, you know?
Yeah. Wait, were we supposed
to get presents?
- They did. They had sexual intercourse.
- What?
- Lily told me.
- No way.
- No, you are so...
- No, I promise.
Why do you make up stuff like that?
- No, I do not. I have a nice car.
- You make shit up.
I didn't say what kind...
Hey.
(INAUDIBLE)
- Good luck in Japan, Rob.
- Good luck tonight, Travis.
HUD: Hey, dude. Dude, dude, dude.
Are you all right, man?
- Hey. Come on.
- This is not the time, Hud.
- What is it, man?
- Let him go.
- We should talk to him.
- We're not talking to him.
I could talk to him now.
Dude, you already talked
to the whole party!
LILY:... have to do something.
JASON: No.
Everyone needs to just calm down
- and give him space.
- LILY: He's just gonna stay
- locked in his room all night?
- Lily, look at you.
- It's fine, trust me.
- It is not fine.
- It is fine.
- You are his brother.
You are his best friend.
Go and make him happy.
HUD: So, how do you wanna do this?
Do you wanna do most of the talking,
or do you want me
to do most of the talking?
- You're not doing any talking.
- Okay, cool.
We got to talk.
You don't know
what you're talking about,
- all right?
- Okay, well, then tell me.
It was just a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Yeah, well, Beth told Lori
that after you guys got together,
- you totally blew her off.
- I didn't blow her off!
She said you never called her.
Look, I'm leaving, all right?
So what am I supposed to do?
I don't know, man.
She was heartbroken.
Look, there's no "together. " It's just
her and me, two separate things.
It's better if we just stay friends.
...not that I feel like I'm not
good enough for her!
No, stop, stop!
I didn't say "feel," Rob.
You're not good enough for her.
That's it. That's fact. That's science.
Beth Mclntyre is, like,
from a whole 'nother planet, man.
She's beautiful. She's charming.
And you... I love you,
but let's face it,
you're kind of a douchebag.
And going to Japan is not gonna fix that.
She's crazy about you, bro.
- Like, right now, as you are.
- HUD: And you're in love with her.
- JASON: But you got to go after her.
- It's not that simple.
- No, it is that simple, Rob.
- HUD: Come on, man. Don't be scared.
It's about moments, man.
That's all that...
You got to learn to say,
"Forget the world,"
and hang on to the people
that you care about the most.
(BUILDING RUMBLING)
HUD: Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God. What the hell was that?
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
HUD: That scared the shit out of me.
JASON: Lil! Lil!
Did you feel that?
It was like an earthquake.
HUD: You guys...
JASON: Lil, where are you?
- What was that?
- HEATHER: What was that?
- JASON: Hey. Are you all right?
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, that was really scary.
- Did you see anything?
Hey, Marlena! Marlena, are you okay?
Guys, look out!
- Okay.
- MAN: It was like a bomb.
JASON: All right, here we go.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Wait. Everyone quiet down. All right?
- But now, just approximately...
- Shut up, shut up.
- ... 15 minutes after word...
- Guys! Come on.
...of a possible earthquake
in lower Manhattan.
Nearby, in New York Harbour, we're
getting word of an oil tanker capsizing
in the middle of the harbour
near the Statue of Liberty.
- Once again...
- HUD: Dude, that's really close.
- ... there's no way to know if any...
- That's really, really close.
That's true. Do you think
we could see something from the roof?
- I don't know. Maybe.
- J, wanna go to the roof?
Let's go see if we can see
something on the roof.
Come on, Jason.
We're not going up to the roof.
- Yeah, let's go up there.
- JENN: I don't think we should.
LILY: No!
ANTONIO: That was really...
WOMAN: What do you think?
Think it's another terrorist attack?
ROB: It's insane, man.
JASON: Watch your step.
It was shaking everywhere, man.
Just like tremors.
- Yeah, it's on the news downstairs.
- Is this the only lights that went out?
- MAN: I think they blew up the trains.
- No, a couple did.
- Some stayed on.
- HUD: Oh, man. What is going on?
Maybe you should've left town
a little bit earlier, right?
Shut up.
(EXPLOSION SOUNDS)
ROB: Oh, my God!
No, no, no.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
JASON: Hud. Move. Hud!
(ALL CLAMOURING)
(HUD PANTING)
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Oh, God.
HUD: Rob, you got a set of keys?
MAN: Get out of here!
Right, did you look back?
Did anybody get hurt?
- Did anybody see Jason or not?
- I don't know.
HUD: Did anybody see Jason?
Has anybody seen Jason?
- Did anybody see Jason?
- Is he inside?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
HUD: Oh, my God! Oh! Oh, shit!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
- Oh, God! Oh, God!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
(HUD GASPING)
Oh, my God!
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
MAN: You gotta take your stuff
and we gotta get out of here, man!
I'm telling you!
- I'm so sorry.
- LILY: Where were you?
(MAN 1 SCREAMING)
Hey, did you guys see that?
Did you guys just see that?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
JASON: Go! Let's go!
- Hey, get down! Get down!
- You all right? You all right?
HUD: Yeah, did you guys see that?
- Did you guys see that?
- ROB: You all right?
There are people still out there.
(LOUD STOMPING)
HUD: Rob! Rob! Hey, Rob, I saw it! Rob!
- Rob.
- What?
- Rob, I saw it!
- What's he saying?
- It's alive.
(PEOPLE COUGHING)
JASON: (MUFFLED) Stay down, Lily!
Get back!
(ROARING)
MAN: He's going away now.
ROB: Jason, what are you doing?
LILY: Jason, where are you going?
Lily, just wait.
(WOMAN CRYING)
- Jason, don't go out...
- LILY: Jason, don't!
Lily, just wait here!
HUD: Hey, Rob! Rob!
Where's he going, dude?
- LILY: Jason!
- Rob. Rob!
(SIRENS WAILING)
- LILY: Oh, my God. Marlena?
- Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Wait, come here. Come here. Sit down.
MAN: It walked right through
that street over there.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
It walked right over my head.
ROB: What?
MAN: That's the sound it's making.
You said you saw something, right?
So what did you see?
- You said it was alive? What was it?
- MAN 1: Who cares what it...
HUD: I don't know, man. I don't know.
I mean, I was taping. I can show you.
Hey, you guys! I have it on tape!
- ROB: Well, then rewind it. Rewind it.
- Yeah. Here, here. Let me rewind it...
It's gonna be a great opportunity for you.
ROB: Yeah, but I don't even
speak the language.
Oh, come on. How hard could it be?
It's Japanese. It's Japanese-hard.
- It'll be fine.
- Do you really think I should go?
- Oh, my God.
- ANTONIO: That makes no sense.
- That makes no sense.
- JENN: Did you see it?
I don't know what it was, of course!
It was giant.
It was like... Did you see that thing?
ANTONIO: I'm not yelling at you,
all right?
JENN: Yes, you are!
Hey, guys, guys, come on!
Everybody just calm down!
- Quiet, guys.
- All right. Come on, just shut up!
All right? We don't know what we saw!
The point is it's still here!
All right? So we need to get
the hell out of Manhattan!
- Now.
- ANTONIO: Yeah, yeah.
JASON: And out to the Brooklyn Bridge.
I think it's the best plan.
- MAN: It's a straight shot to Delancey.
- Just take the Williamsburg.
No. Do you know how far that is?
Brooklyn is right there.
No, no, no, dude. It's so much closer.
It's right here.
- Centre Street's like a block away.
- What's going on?
HUD: I think we're gonna get out of here.
Is she okay to...
Okay, yeah. Yeah, okay. Marlena,
we're gonna get out of here, okay?
It was eating people.
It was eating everyone.
ROB: We gotta go! Go! Let's go!
LILY: Okay, come here.
ROB: Go, go, go, go, go.
MARLENA: I don't think...
Don't even look.
ROB: Is anyone's phone working?
JASON: What?
- Hud, is your phone working?
- What?
- No...
- Shit! I left it in the apartment.
- There's no signal.
- You're not getting a signal either?
LILY: No, no, come on.
- JASON: Hud, come on!
- What? Okay.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
MAN 1: It's all right.
MAN 2: Let's go.
PARAMEDIC: We need an IV.
MAN 1: Calm down, please.
MAN 2: Let's go, people.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- HUD: Excuse me, Officer.
Do you know...
What was that thing? What was it?
Look, if you're not injured,
you got to keep moving, man.
Let's go! Let's go, people! Let's go!
MAN 3: Yeah, once we get to the bridge,
we'll be safe.
Hey, how are you? Is she doing better?
LILY: She's okay. She's gonna be fine.
- Marlena, you saw it. What was that?
- LILY: Not now, Hud.
Sorry.
MAN ON PA:
Please go in an orderly manner.
Continue moving south
towards Brooklyn.
JASON: Just keep going.
ANTONIO: Yeah, I don't know. It got hit.
MAN 4: Once we get over there,
I'll go to my cousin's house.
She has a condo. She's out of town.
MAN ON PA: I repeat, do not stop.
Keep moving.
There will be instructions
on the Brooklyn side...
Get across the bridge.
Move in a quick and orderly fashion.
- ROB: You still filming?
- Yeah.
People are gonna wanna know
how it all went down.
Well, you can just tell them
how it all went down, Hud.
No, that wouldn't work.
People need to see this, you know?
This is gonna be important.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I mean, people are gonna watch this.
ROB: Beth? Beth?
HUD: Rob!
ROB: Beth, I've been trying to reach you.
Are you okay? Hello?
HUD: Wait a second, you guys!
Look, hey! Lily, stop!
ROB: I'm sorry. It's really loud here.
Can you speak up?
HUD: Lily!
- What?
- Rob got a hold of Beth.
LILY: Wait! Jason, wait!
- Rob's got Beth on the phone!
- What'd you say?
- What?
- OFFICER: Hey, y'all, come on.
Rob's got Beth on the phone!
Okay, Beth, you're gonna
have to calm down, okay?
Where are you?
What do you mean, you can't move?
- What?
- MAN ON PA: I repeat, no panicking.
(LOUD RUMBLING)
MAN 1: Did you see it?
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
- LILY: Jason!
- Can you see anything?
HUD: No, I can't get over there!
I can't... I can't see anything!
Can you see it?
LILY: Jason!
- Why did you stop?
- LILY: Jason!
- What?
- Jason, watch out!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
LILY: Jason! No, Jason! No!
Jason!
- No, no! God! No, Jason! Jason!
- MARLENA: Lily, come on!
Jason! No!
(BRIDGE CABLES GROANING)
(BRIDGE CABLES SNAPPING)
(HUD GASPING)
Go, go, go, go!
(HUD GROANING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
MARLENA: Lily. Lily, wait. Stop!
Turn around and listen to me right now.
Would somebody please,
please tell me what just happened?
- I don't know.
- I mean, it came out of nowhere!
And he was there
and then he was gone!
- My God! Jason! Jason!
- MARLENA: Lily, I'm so, so sorry.
HUD: (PANTING) Rob.
You got to listen to me, man.
I am so sorry about your brother.
I'm sorry, man. I'm so sorry.
Are you okay? Rob?
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
- Rob. Rob, dude.
- MARLENA: We can't stay here.
We can't.
HUD: (PANTING) Rob.
We got to get out of here, man.
Listen to me.
We got... We got to get moving, man.
We go to the Manhattan Bridge,
you know?
We got to get out of here.
It's not safe here.
Okay, we can go to the other side.
We can try and get
to the Lincoln Tunnel.
I don't know, man. I don't know, but...
Dude, we got to get out of here.
It's not safe here.
(LILY SOBBING)
What are we gonna do, Rob?
What are we gonna do?
Do you know? Hey!
Look... Hey, Jesus. Rob. Hey, Rob?
- No.
- Rob!
- My battery's dead.
- Yeah, dude, I...
Well, listen, we got
to get out of here, man. You know?
- Rob! Rob!
- MARLENA: Well, where's he going?
Where are you going?
HUD: Oh, God. I'll go get him. Hey, Rob!
Rob! Dude!
I can't take all this running, man!
Hey, Rob.
Excuse me. Hey, Rob!
The store's closed, man!
- Rob, Rob!
- NEWSCASTER:... burning right now.
The bridge was filled
with pedestrians travelling across.
- It has collapsed.
- Holy shit.
No word on injuries yet, but...
Oh, God.
NEWSCASTER 1: We continue now
with our breaking news story
in lower Manhattan.
We are getting some truly extraordinary
live images here in the studio.
For those of you just joining us,
lower Manhattan is
in an absolute state of siege
in what has been...
MAN ON PA:
This is a mandatory evacuation.
Proceed south immediately.
(CREATURE ROARING)
Get out of the city in an orderly fashion.
This is a mandatory evacuation!
We need everyone out of this area now!
Rob? Rob! Hey, dude!
Actually, I think we need to get out
of here, like, right now!
Do you know what I'm saying?
Because there's some
serious shit going on outside!
Rob? No, like, you know what I mean?
Rob, like, there's some strange
shit going on! Rob?
NEWSCASTER 2: Donna Martel
is near the scene at City Hall.
HUD: What's going on?
Can you tell us what it looks like
on the ground there?
MARTEL: Well, Bob, the military will not
let us get too close,
but from what we can see,
there's clearly a sizable mobilisation
of troops and equipment,
and they're trying to get everyone
to leave the area...
NEWSCASTER 3: To be honest, Tom,
your guess is as good as mine
at this point.
There appears to be
something coming off of it.
And the ground seems
to be covered in debris...
NEWSCASTER 2: It looks like
there's something falling of it, doesn't it?
MARTEL: Yes. Yes. Yes, it does.
There are pieces falling
all over the street.
- HUD: Oh, my God.
- Whatever they are, they are moving.
- Oh, my God! They're...
- NEWSCASTER 2: Donna!
- They're right there!
- HUD: Oh, shit.
- Donna, can you hear us?
- MARLENA: Hey!
What are you doing?
We got to get out of here! Where is he?
I know, that's what I've been telling him.
- MARLENA: Rob! Rob!
- I've been trying to do that!
Rob. Rob. We gotta go right now, okay?
- The military's evacuating everyone.
- HUD: Hey, Rob, listen to me, okay?
We gotta get out of here.
It's time to leave the electronics store.
MARLENA: Rob, come on. We got to go.
- Just come on. Let's go...
- ROB: Just stop it!
Okay? Stop, wait!
VOICE ON MACHINE:
To listen to your messages...
BETH: (CRYING) Rob! Rob! I can't...
Oh, God! I can't move.
It fell. My apartment...
The whole wall fell on me!
I'm bleeding! I'm bleeding. I can't move.
Oh, my God.
Help me, Rob.
VOICE ON MACHINE:
To delete this message...
HUD: Rob, wait up! Rob!
ROB: I got your message,
and I'm on my way there, okay?
HUD: Hey, Rob, listen.
You got to think this through, man.
Okay? Beth lives in Midtown.
Midtown is that way.
- Guess what else is that way?
- MARLENA: Will you wait up?
HUD: Some horrific shit is in Midtown!
MARLENA: This is insane, okay?
We're not gonna go
near that thing, okay?
to the middle of the city!
No, we're not.
You're not coming with me.
Look. Fall in with the military.
Fall in with the crowd.
Let them gonna escort you out of here.
Okay?
- HUD: Rob!
- I'm sorry. I got to go.
Rob!
- Rob! Listen!
- MARLENA: Rob, wait a minute!
One of us is gonna have to tackle you,
and that's gonna be very uncomfortable
for everybody involved!
Listen, you can't talk me out of it, okay?
Look at me. This is not me crazy.
All right? I know what I'm doing.
And you can't talk me out of it.
- So turn around, go...
- LILY: I'm coming.
I'm coming with you.
ROB: Lily, you don't have to do that.
No, I want to. I'm coming.
MARLENA: Guys, did you not hear
her message?
I mean, even if we get to Beth's,
there's a chance
- that she's already...
- ROB: Shut up.
MARLENA: Guys, this is insane.
- HUD: Rob!
- You know what I'm talking about, right?
MARLENA: You can't possibly think
that this is a good idea.
HUD: Rob! Rob!
- Rob!
- MARLENA: Hey... Hold...
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I'm sorry, I don't understand you.
Yeah, but I don't understand you.
Rob, hold up!
Look, I'm sorry. Hey, listen to me. Man.
- Hud!
- I'm so sorry.
Hey, Rob! Wait up, please!
Rob! Have you tried maybe calling 911,
- see if somebody else can get there?
- Yeah, I tried!
Okay, well. I mean, what about police?
Fire department?
- I couldn't get through! I tried, I...
- Okay, it just seems a little...
(SCREECHING)
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, my God!
(MONSTER ROARING)
HUD: (GASPING) Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Rob! Rob! Hey, Rob!
- Hud! We're gonna go this way!
- I can't hear you!
- Subway!
- What? What?
- Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
- Come on! Come on!
This shit is crazy, dude!
(ROARING)
Oh, Rob, dude. There's like...
(HUD GROANING)
Hud! Hud!
Are you okay, man? You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm all right.
- ROB: Come on.
- Okay. Okay. Oh, God damn.
- ROB: Oh, shit.
(ALL PANTING)
HUD: What the hell was that?
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- LILY: Did you see that?
- Oh, my God. Oh, God.
- Did you see that?
Okay.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
Hey, look. We can just cross...
We can just cross to the other platform,
then go up the stairs and see
if the other side of the street...
Rob, the other side of the street
looks the same as this side!
We can wait for there to be a lull,
and then make a break for it!
Rob, the air caught on fire!
Okay? There's not gonna be a lull!
But if we wait on the other...
Listen to me, man,
I am with you, okay? I really, really am.
I'm just saying, you gotta listen
to what's going on up there.
- We can't...
- LILY: Rob, he's right, okay?
We have to wait. We have to wait.
HUD: This is insane.
Shit!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Oh, God.
- What? Rob, what?
Hey, Mom.
Yeah, no. I'm okay. Okay, yeah, we are.
We're being evacuated right now.
The army's here.
We're being evacuated, so don't worry.
Okay, but Mom... Mom, listen.
We tried to get out of the city,
and we took the Brooklyn Bridge,
and we were right there when it hit.
Jason's dead. Jason's dead, Mom.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(SOFTLY) I don't know
what to say to him.
You know?
Like, I feel like I should say something,
but I don't know what to say.
I'm not even supposed to be here.
You didn't have to be. I mean,
you had your chance in the alley.
You could've left us.
Yeah, you were supposed to meet up
with some friends or something, right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
LILY: This isn't a bad idea.
ROB: Just walk.
LILY: Wait, so then...
HUD: What's going on?
I don't know.
(ROB CHATTERING)
ROB:... just go across here.
LILY: That's good.
Yeah. This is the six.
Rob, I don't think the trains
are running right now, man.
- No, we can just walk the track, see?
- Yeah.
Look. Beth lives here, Columbus Circle.
We can just walk down the six
to Lexington and then walk down
Central Park South.
MARLENA: You want us to
walk in the tunnels?
It's either that or stay here.
(LOUD RUMBLING)
HUD: I'll walk the tunnels.
MARLENA: I can't see.
HUD: It's kind of freaking me out,
you know?
ROB: I think there's a light
on the camera.
- Let me see.
- LILY: There is?
Yeah, right here. See?
Okay.
HUD: Ocean is big, dude.
All I'm saying is a couple of years ago,
they found a fish in Madagascar
that they thought
- had been extinct for centuries.
- ROB: So what?
It's been down there this whole time,
and nobody noticed?
Sure. Maybe it erupted
from an ocean trench, you know?
Or a crevasse. Crevice.
It's just a theory.
I mean, for all we know,
it's from another planet and it flew here.
- Like Superman?
- HUD: Yeah, exactly like...
Wait. You know who Superman is?
Oh, my God.
You know who Superman is?
- Okay, I'm not...
- I'm, like, feeling something.
- Are you aware of Garfield?
- HUD: A lot of people think
he's from a planet
that he's not actually from.
ROB: I just can't stop thinking about
how the last thing I said to her was,
"Good luck tonight, Travis. "
She knows you didn't mean that.
LILY: When I think of some of the things
I said to Jason...
- ROB: No, that's different.
- Why?
Jason knew you loved him.
HUD: Hey, do you guys remember
a couple of years ago, when that guy
was lighting homeless people
on fire in the subways?
- Jesus, Hud.
- What?
It's maybe not the best topic
for conversation down here.
Right.
I just can't stop thinking how scary
it would be if a flaming homeless guy
- came out of the dark right now.
- Hud, seriously.
- Seriously.
- I'm just saying. Sorry.
(CLANGING)
- What was that?
- Let's just keep moving.
Holy shit! Oh, God, this is nasty.
This is disgusting.
HUD: They're all running
in the same direction.
- Yeah, like they're running away.
- LILY: From what?
HUD: Hey, how much farther?
I don't know.
Let's get out at the next station.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
(HISSING)
Did you guys hear that?
LILY: What is that?
MARLENA: Just listen.
HUD: I don't see anything. Do you guys?
(MARLENA HUSHING)
(HUD BREATHING HEAVILY)
HUD: Oh, man, this is the worst.
MARLENA: Will you be quiet
for five seconds?
ROB: Oh, turn on the night vision.
HUD: What?
- What do you mean?
- It's right here.
I got it. It's right here. There.
Is it on?
- HUD: Oh, shit.
- What? What?
- Run. Okay, run. Okay, run.
- What?
Hey, let's start running! Just run!
Just run! Just start running right now!
Start running now! Run, run, run!
Run! Just run!
MARLENA: Lily!
HUD: You guys!
(HISSING)
HUD: Wait.
Oh, God! Help!
Please help! You guys, help!
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(MARLENA SCREAMING)
HUD: Marlena! Here!
Come on. Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Hud!
(SCREECHING)
- ROB:... there you go.
- Totally not what I was thinking...
(ALL PANTING)
How are you doing over there, Marlena?
You okay?
You tell me.
How does it look?
HUD: Looks like it hurts.
What do you mean? You're saying
this isn't attractive, like, at all?
A little bit.
(GRUNTS)
- Here. Here, here. You can wash it off.
- MARLENA: Thanks.
ROB: Here. Did it get you, Hud?
Did it bite you, man?
No, it didn't get me.
Okay. Okay.
Hey. Hey.
So those things
came out of nowhere, right?
- Yeah.
- Oh, man.
That one that grabbed me,
it was trying to drag me away.
What's up with that?
- Maybe it liked you, Hud.
- Yeah.
Maybe it was trying
to make me its queen.
Hey, thanks for coming back
and helping me out, you know?
What? You think that I'm the kind
of person that wouldn't do that?
No. No. I know you aren't.
I was just saying, like, I'm glad you did.
Otherwise,
I would have been totally dead.
Right?
It's okay. You just got bit.
LILY: Hey.
HUD: Marlena's hurt pretty bad,
you know?
Well, we could wait here
for a little bit, I guess,
and just hope those things
don't make it through the door.
- Yeah, okay. What's the next option?
- Well.
Okay, we could see
what's out through this way.
- Maybe find another tunnel.
- LILY: No, no more tunnels.
Then, I don't know.
We try our luck up top.
HUD: Okay, just to be clear,
so our options are
die here, die in the tunnels,
or die in the streets. Is that...
- Yeah, pretty much.
- ... pretty much the summing up of it?
But wait, we don't even know
where we are, right?
So, let's just go up and look around.
See if we recognise anything.
Do you think you'll be okay to walk?
- No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- HUD: Here, I'll help you.
ROB: We're at 59th.
LILY: We're at 59th.
HUD: Yeah.
ROB: We're at 59th.
ROB: That's weird.
HUD: What?
Yeah.
ROB: Hello!
HUD: Marlena?
LILY: What's wrong?
HUD: Are you okay?
I'm really... I'm dizzy.
ROB: Yeah. Do you wanna
sit down for a second?
- No, I'm fine.
- LILY: She needs a doctor.
- You sure?
- I'm totally fine.
You know, 'cause we could
sit down if you want to.
No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
PRYCE: We've got civilians!
Are there any more of you?
ROB: No, just us four.
LILY: It's just us.
PRYCE: We got four civilians here.
- MAN ON RADIO: Okay, bring them in.
- Roger.
PRYCE: Let's go, move. Move it.
LILY: Okay, okay.
- Let's go!
- Okay, okay.
ROB: Excuse me, sir? Sir? Excuse me.
Listen, we need your help.
Our friend, she's hurt. She's trapped
in her building right by here,
at Columbus Circle.
That is not
where you wanna be right now.
LILY: Do you guys know what it is?
Out there?
Do you know what that thing is?
If they know, they ain't telling me.
Whatever it is, it's winning.
(PEOPLE GROANING)
MAN 1: What's up?
MAN 2: We got another bite here.
HUD: Don't look at that. Gross.
ROB: Please, we can't stay here.
We have...
PRYCE: Hey, not now.
MAN 3: Copy that.
MAN 4: Sir, we have two F-18s
on route from Selfridge.
Four more are arming up,
- maybe 30 minutes out.
- MAN 4: Roger that.
Listen up, people.
Rack them and pack them.
- We're phantoms in 15.
- ROB: Sir.
- Where the hell did you find them?
- PRYCE: They were in the tunnels.
ROB: Yeah, we had to walk all the way
from Spring Street.
Get them ready for transport,
put them on the evac chopper.
- Yes, sir. Let's move. Move, move.
- ROB: No, wait. Wait.
- Listen, our friend is very badly hurt.
- Move it.
- PRYCE: Move. Move.
- We have to get to her.
Sorry, son, can't help you.
Get them on the chopper.
No, but, please, listen to me. Let go!
Just listen for a second, please!
GRAFF: Turn that goddamned camera...
LILY: We've been trying to
get to her all...
ROB: Make our own way.
No, do you have a...
GRAFF: I am not
jeopardising this operation,
- or my men.
- ROB: I don't want your help.
GRAFF: You are getting on
that chopper now.
ROB: I just need you to listen to me
for one second, sir.
- You have no idea what's out there.
- ROB: I don't care what's out there.
Listen to me. She's dying.
GRAFF: There is nothing I can do
about that now.
The girl that I love more than anything
is dying and it's my fault.
She should have been with me tonight,
and I let her go and...
And I get it, okay?
You have your hands full. I get that.
I get that, but we're gonna go after her,
and if you wanna stop me,
- then you're gonna have to shoot me.
- MARLENA: Hud.
- I don't feel so good.
- Oh, shit.
- Bite! We've got a bite!
- Marlena.
- HUD: Hold on a second.
- PARAMEDIC: Get her moving.
Keep moving!
HUD: Hey, Marlena, are you okay?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Hold on a second.
Where are you taking her?
Hold on a second. Wait!
Oh my God, wait!
- Marlena, stop! Just wait a second!
- ROB: Let me go.
- Just wait a second. Please.
- Wait! Marlena!
- PARAMEDIC: Get out of the way.
HUD: Marlena! Hold on a second!
- Just wait a... Let go of me! Stop it!
- No.
(MARLENA GROANING)
HUD: God! Please, God!
Where are you taking Marlena?
Wait a second.
(ALL CLAMOURING)
It's over. There is nothing you can do.
There is nothing you can do
for her now. It is over. It's over.
- Rogers, clear out of here.
- You sure?
I'll get them to the choppers from here.
- Let's move out.
- HUD: (GASPING) Oh, my God.
What just happened?
PRYCE: Let's go.
I shouldn't be doing this shit.
- Come on. Come on.
- HUD: Okay.
- Let's go. Move.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go, move. Come on.
PRYCE: You gotta listen to me.
This girl, her building,
it's at Columbus Circle?
- Yeah?
- If you wanna go out in this,
I ain't gonna stop you.
But you gotta know something.
The government's considering
the Hammer Down protocol,
which means they're willing
to let this whole area go.
- You mean Midtown?
- No, I mean Manhattan.
Come on. We're taking
one last shot at this thing.
- Oh, God.
- If that doesn't work,
they're levelling
the whole goddamned city.
- Your watch is still working?
- Yeah?
All right. The airlifts are leaving
from 40th and Park.
Last chopper's wheels-up
at exactly 0600.
If you can make it there,
then they'll get you out.
- Okay. Okay, thank you.
-58th Street's right there.
- Now, go. Move, move, move.
- ROB: Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Go, go, go.
- This is like a nightmare, you know.
- It all happened so fast,
I couldn't even really see
what happened to her.
I mean, did you see it?
Could you see what happened, Hud?
No, her eyes started bleeding, and then
they were screaming she was bitten.
(SOBBING) And then she wouldn't
stop bleeding. And then...
LILY: Hud.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay. I'm okay.
Look, guys, I don't mean to be...
But we don't have a lot of time.
Okay, so maybe you guys
should just stay here, and I'll go.
All right?
- I'm sorry. I just...
- No, no, we're coming. We're coming.
Are you sure?
No, no, man.
No, we have to do this, okay?
We're with you. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go right now.
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
ROB: Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
HUD: What?
- Oh, my God.
- What is it? What?
- Shit.
- That's not Beth's place, is it?
- LILY: Oh, my God.
- Is that Beth's apartment?
ROB: Oh, my God.
HUD: Rob. Is that her place?
- Tell me that's not her place.
- ROB: That's her place, yeah.
HUD: Oh, shit. I don't suppose
she lives on the ground floor.
ROB: No, 39th.
- Oh, great.
- LILY: How do we even get up there?
ROB: I don't know. We just go inside
and then see how high we can get.
I don't know if I can do that.
HUD: Well, maybe we could try going up
the other building,
and then see if there's a place
to cross over onto her roof.
And then we could find some way
down to her place.
(HELICOPTERS WHIRRING)
HUD: Wait. No, never mind.
No, that's a bad idea.
Hey, that's a bad idea. I take that back.
No one ever listens to me, ever.
And now, of course, they listen to me.
Great.
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
ROB: Shit. Shit.
(SWITCHES CLICKING)
LILY: Probably not working.
- HUD: What's going on?
- Not working.
Wait, wait. Let's just... Maybe...
- No? No?
- Shit.
LILY: Well, why don't
you take the stairs?
HUD: You guys see that guy's face
when Lily asked him what it was?
I mean, they have no idea.
- Unless they're, like, in on it.
- Jesus, Hud.
I don't read the papers.
- Maybe our government made this thing.
- ROB: Oh, yeah.
I mean, you know,
maybe it was an accident,
- or maybe it was on purpose...
- ROB: Sure, maybe they did.
- Does it really matter right now?
- HUD: Yeah.
It matters because I need to talk
about something.
Otherwise, I'm actually probably
going to shit my pants in this stairwell.
(ALL PANTING)
HUD: I'm sorry.
(WIND WHISTLING)
Hey, wait, wait. You guys hear that?
You guys hear that?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think we're getting close.
Hud, I'm gonna check this floor.
LILY: Okay.
Okay, like, I think it's like,
two more up, I think.
LILY: (GASPING) Okay.
ROB: Guys, guys, guys.
This one, it's got to be.
It's got to be this one.
(HUD COUGHING)
(EMERGENCY POWER ALARM
BEEPING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
HUD: Oh, God.
I don't think there's anybody here. No.
- Oh, Jesus.
- LILY: Oh, my God.
LILY: Oh, my God.
ROB: Okay.
Okay, now, we can do this.
We can totally do this.
- LILY: I don't know, Rob.
- Look, it's a straight shot.
- (STUTTERING) I don't know. I'm sorry.
- Lily, Lily, it's a straight shot.
Look, it's a straight shot.
We could use... There's pipes there.
We could use
the air conditioners. Okay?
Come on. We came this far.
We can do it. I'll go first.
- LILY: Okay, okay, okay. Yes.
- All right? Okay.
- HUD: Okay, I'll document it.
- Be careful, okay?
- Come on. Come on.
- Okay. Okay.
Okay. Hud, come on!
Put the camera down! Come on!
HUD: Oh, Jesus.
LILY: Okay. All right. Okay.
ROB: I'll go first.
All right. If this is the last thing you see,
that means I died.
- ROB: Hud, come on!
- Okay.
HUD: Look out! Oh, shit...
Okay.
(LILY GRUNTING)
ROB: Okay. Okay.
LILY: Shit.
(FIGHTER JETS ROARING)
- Okay. Okay.
- HUD: (WHISPERING) Oh, God.
(GRUNTING)
- Yes. Okay. You all right?
- Yeah.
We're almost there, come on.
Come on, Hud.
(ALL PANTING)
Shit.
ROB: Beth! Beth! Beth!
(EMERGENCY POWER ALARM
BEEPING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
LILY: Can you get it?
HUD: Do you need help?
Do you need help? Or...
(ROB GRUNTING)
(STRONG WIND WHISTLING)
ROB: Beth? Beth?
Beth?
Beth? Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
LILY: What?
ROB: Shit.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Beth.
ROB: Beth.
HUD: What?
ROB: Beth!
LILY: Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Can you hear me? Beth.
BETH: (FAINTLY) Hey.
- Are you really here?
- Yeah, I'm really here.
Rob?
You came back for me.
Of course I came back for you.
- I'm sorry it took me so long.
- No, it's okay.
Okay, okay, okay. You're okay.
We're gonna get you out of here, okay?
We'll get you out, all right?
Hud, put the camera down
- and help me, okay?
- Okay, okay.
(BETH GROANING)
ROB: It'll be okay.
LILY: Okay, here we go.
- If we all just lift at the same time.
- Hold on, okay. We got you.
- All right? We have to.
- BETH: Don't do that, Rob.
- Please don't do that.
- ROB: It's gonna be over in a second.
- All right?
- LILY: Okay. Ready, guys?
BETH: (SOBBING) No, please. No.
HUD: Slowly. It's okay.
We're gonna do it real slow.
- Easy, easy, just wait.
- BETH: No, don't.
ROB: One, two, three.
LILY: One, two, three.
(BETH SCREAMS)
BETH: (CLENCHING TEETH) Oh, God.
(HELICOPTERS WHIRRING)
LILY: Okay, now, sit down. Sit down.
ROB: I know. I know. Here.
LILY: I know. I know. You're gonna
be okay. You're gonna be okay.
(CONTINUES GROANING)
- You're gonna be fine.
- BETH: No, no, no.
I know, I know, I know it hurts.
I know it hurts.
(MONSTER ROARING)
BETH: What is that?
- God.
- HUD: It's a terrible thing.
LILY: Okay. We gotta go. We gotta go.
ROB: Okay. Let's go.
- I got you.
- HUD: Oh, God.
- Oh, God.
- ROB: All right. All right. Go, go, go.
HUD: Go.
ROB: Okay. I got you.
ROB: You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay, all right?
Just hold on to me.
You're gonna be all right.
You're gonna be okay, all right?
You're gonna be okay.
(BETH CONTINUES GROANING)
- Okay. Hang on to me.
- BETH: Oh, my God.
- Okay, okay.
- Oh, my God.
(ALL PANTING)
Okay.
HUD: Oh, shit. Man, this is unbelievable.
- Are you okay?
- Just don't look down, okay?
- I can't help it.
- You're all right. You're all right.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God!
- HUD: Okay, let's go.
- Keep moving, just go.
Go, just go. Just go, go, go. Go.
Just get to the other side.
Come on, just keep moving.
(LOUD EXPLOSIONS)
HUD: Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit!
- ROB: Oh, my God!
HUD: Oh, my God. Did you see that?
ROB: Okay, come on.
LILY: Get inside.
ROB: Okay. Come on, come on.
- Oh, God.
- ROB: Go! Go!
(MONSTER ROARING)
LILY: Run! Run! Hurry!
(ALL PANTING)
- Rob, come on!
- HUD: (PANTING) Oh, my God.
(CREATURE CHITTERING)
(CREATURE SQUEALING)
HUD: Oh, my God.
BETH: What the hell was that?
HUD: I don't know.
Something else also terrible.
HUD: Rob, what time
do the choppers take off?
-0600.
- What time is that?
-6:00, Hud.
- Yeah, okay. I knew that.
- Come on, come on.
- HUD: Okay.
(MACHINE GUNS FIRING)
(SCREECHING)
(MONSTER SCREECHING)
Wait up!
ROB: Did we make it?
HUD: We want to get out of here,
come on.
ROB: Let's go! Let's go!
Keep your heads down.
BETH: Come on! Come on!
You guys are on the next chopper.
- ROB: No!
- Clear this area. Clear this area.
ROB: No, no, wait. Wait.
BETH: Lily!
ROB: We'll be right behind you, okay?
Wait for us. Wait for us.
We'll be right behind you.
We're gonna be okay. All right?
We're gonna be all right, you hear me?
(SCREECHING)
ROB: Oh, God! Jesus Christ!
Stay low. Stay low.
Come on, come on, come on.
Thank you.
(MONSTER GROWLING)
- PILOT: They're starting the bomb run.
- Get them out of here. Get going.
HUD: Oh, shit. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Are you guys seeing this right now?
Are you seeing this right now?
Look, look, look.
Are you seeing this shit right now?
Oh, my God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
(ROARING)
Oh, God.
Those aren't gonna hit us, are they?
Oh, my God. They hit it!
They just hit it right now!
Look, you guys, they just hit it!
They hit it with... Oh, my God!
- Yeah, they hit it, you guys! They hit it!
- Oh, he's going down.
PILOT: (ON RADIO) Target down.
Target down. Target down. He's down.
HUD: (STUTTERING)
I think they got him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
That's the shit right there!
That's what I'm talking about...
Oh, my God! Oh, no, no, no!
(BETH SCREAMING)
(EMERGENCY ALARM BLARING)
HUD: Oh, my God. Oh my God.
God, please, God.
(SOBBING) Please, God. Please.
Please, God and Jesus.
Jesus Christ, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, God. Please, no.
Help me, Rob!
Rob. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
(SCREAMING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(STATIC ON RADIO)
MAN ON RADIO: This is Hawkeye 6.
Target still active.
Initiating Hammer Down.
TOT, 15 minutes.
Sirens will sound two minutes out.
If you can hear those sirens,
you're in the blasting zone.
BETH: Come on. Come on. Hud.
Hud, are you okay?
- HUD: Yeah, all right. I guess. I think so.
- I can't move my arm.
- This is Duncan-Charlie, return to base.
- BETH: Help me, you got to help me.
- God help us.
- HUD: Okay. Okay, okay.
BETH: Come on, help me.
(BETH GRUNTING)
I know, I know. We're gonna
get you out of here. Come on.
Hud, come over to the other side.
You've got to pull him up.
Come on, come on.
HUD: Okay, okay.
ROB: I don't think I can move.
BETH: Yes, you can. Don't say that.
MAN ON RADIO:
Copy your last, we're on the move.
- Here, take his hand. Take his hand.
- Good luck.
HUD: Hold on, I got it. I got it. I got it.
Come on, come on.
(SCREAMING)
BETH: I got his legs, go!
(HUD PANTING)
ROB: (GROANING) My leg!
BETH: I know. I know, I know. I know.
It's okay, you're fine. You're good.
You're okay. You're okay.
HUD: I'm gonna have to
stop the bleeding, okay? Okay?
ROB: I'm not okay.
I'm not gonna be able to walk.
BETH: You are going to be able to walk.
Don't do it.
(ROB SCREAMING)
HUD: Okay. All right, listen,
we got to get out of here, okay?
BETH: Well, which way do we go?
HUD: We have to get away from here,
because I think it's gonna explode.
ROB: Okay, okay. Okay.
HUD: All right? Come on. Let's go.
Let's go this way. Come on.
Come on, you can walk. Okay.
Come on. Hold on, wait a second.
- Hud!
What? Oh! Oh, no!
BETH: Hud! Hud!
ROB: Hud, what are you doing?
(HUD WHIMPERING)
(SNORTING)
(HUD SHUDDERING)
ROB: Hud!
(HUD SCREAMING)
(LENS WHIRRING)
Hud!
Hud! Hud!
(BETH PANTING)
(MONSTER ROARING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(BETH SOBBING)
ROB: He's gone.
He's gone.
- They're all gone.
- I know.
(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE)
BETH: (SOBBING) We gotta go.
We gotta go. We gotta get out of here.
ROB: Where? There's nowhere to go to.
BETH: We got to go.
He's coming towards us.
ROB: No, we should just wait here.
Just wait here.
Listen, we wait here,
they'll find us, all right?
They're fighting him right now.
If we wait here, they'll find us.
No, we can't stay.
(MONSTER SCREECHING)
It's okay. It's okay.
- I'm so scared.
- I know. I know. I know.
(ROB HUSHING)
(SIREN SOUNDING)
My name is Robert Hawkins.
It's 6:42 a. m. on Saturday, May 23.
Approximately seven hours ago,
something attacked the city.
I don't know what it is.
If you found this tape... I mean,
if you're watching this right now,
then you probably know more
about it than I do.
Whatever it is,
it killed my brother, Jason Hawkins.
It killed my best friend, Hudson Platt,
and Marlena Diamond,
and many, many others.
We've crashed here in Central Park
and taken shelter under this bridge.
The military has begun
bombing the creature
and we're caught in the middle.
Okay. Ready?
(BETH SOBBING)
ROB: It's okay.
- Beth, look at me.
- I don't know what to say.
Well, just tell them who you are.
My name is Elizabeth Mclntyre.
I don't know why this is happening.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
But we're gonna wait here
until this passes.
Rob, we're gonna wait here.
(BETH SCREAMS)
(MONSTER ROARING)
(BETH SCREAMING)
ROB: Look at me, Beth.
Look at me. Look at me.
- I love you.
ROB: I know what I'm talking about.
Come on, admit it.
You are going to miss me
a little bit, right?
BETH: Yeah, we'll see.
(CAMERA BEEPING)
ROB: Okay, yeah, all right.
All right, we're almost out of tape.
We got, like, three seconds left.
What do you wanna say?
Last thing to the camera.
I had a good day.
(CAMERA BEEPS)